Guide to the Johan Kugelberg punk collection, circa 1974-1986.
Kugelberg, Johan punk collection
- Series II. Fliers and Posters
  - Bad Religion, 1983; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Additional bands or artists: Faction, Hated Principle, Anarchistic Youth
    Main text: Into the unknown
  - Bad Religion, 1983; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Additional bands or artists: DI's, Batalion of Saints, Shadow Minstrels, Stains, Angry Samoans, Oddsquad, Kommunity FK, Circle of One, Manifest Destiny, Stalag 13, Whipping Boy, Phillip Blues, El Martio, Social Distortion, Eddie and the Subtitles, Lucky Strike
    Main text: The Vex presents …
  - Bags, The, 1987; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Additional bands or artists: Shock, The Controllers
    Main text: At the Whisky: The Bags…
  - Bags, The, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: Long Goodbye
    Location: Portland, OR
    Additional bands or artists: Neoboys, Bop Zombie
    Main text: The Bags with Neoboys & Bop Zombies
  - Batalion of Saints, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Artist: Bobby Lane
    Venue: North Park Lions Club
    Location: San Diego, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Youth Brigade, Red Scare, Catch-22
    Main text: Dead or alive
  - Batalion of Saints, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Artist: D. Brandt
    Additional bands or artists: Circle One, Whipping Boy, Stalag 13, Manifest Destiny
    Main text: P.U.N.X. presents Battalion of Saints
  - Big Boys, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: Club Foot
    Location: San Francisco, CA or Austin, TX
    Additional bands or artists: Jitters
    Main text: See/Hear/Believe
  - Big Boys, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: Studio 29
    Location: Austin, TX
    Main text: The Big Boys and the Jitters
  - Black Flag, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: Sanata Monica Civic
    Additional bands or artists: Adolescents, DOA, Minutemen
    Main text: KROQ in assoc. with Phantom and Bunko Present - Black Flag
  - Black Flag, 1986; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Artist: Glen E. Friedman (photo)
    Venue: Video Circuit
    Location: Van Nuys, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Painted Willie, Gone
    Main text: Black Flag, Painted Willie, Gone - invite you to a free show for a live album video taping at: Video Circuit
  - Black Flag, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Artist: [Raymond Pettibon?]
    Venue: RRZ
    Location: San Francisco, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Violent Femmes, Murder, Exitus, Sabotage, Control, Crucifix, Channel 3, Battalion of Saints, 7 Seconds, Los Olvidados, Fear, Silvertone, The Untouchables
    Main text: Black Flag - The Violent Femmes …
    Notes: The background of the flier reproduces several Raymond Pettibon fliers; it is unclear if this is a Pettibon design itself.
  - Black Flag, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: Adams Avenue Theatre
    Additional bands or artists: Saccharine Trust, The Front
    Main text: The Maze presents Black Flag - Snowman has a mask he is going to steal some food
  - Black Flag, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: Dancing Waters
    Location: San Pedro, CA
    Main text: Dancing Waters: Black Flag - TV party + beer
  - Black Flag, 1982; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Artist: Raymond Pettibon
    Venue: S.I.R.
    Additional bands or artists: DOA, Wasted Youth, Descendents
    Main text: A goldenvoice production - long live crime - Black Flag
  - Black Flag, 1982; 8.5 x 3.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: Left Bank and My Father's Place
    Location: Mt. Vernon and Roslyn Village, NY
    Additional bands or artists: Saccharine Trust, Angelic Upstarts, Minor Threat
    Main text: Black Flag and Saccharine Trust
  - Black Flag, 1980; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: Fleetwood
    Location: Redondo Beach, CA
    Main text: Black Flag at the Fleetwood
    Notes: With manuscript correction to second date: "Friday June 10th" corrected to "Friday June 6th."
  - Black Flag, 1984; 4.5 x 5.25 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: Hollywood Palladium
    Main text: Avalon Attractions - Black Flag at the Hollywood Palladium
  - Black Flag, 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Additional bands or artists: Dickies, Vandles [Vandals?], Tupelo Chain Sex, Elysian Fields, Dicks, Saccharine Trust, Red Kross, Nip Drivers
    Main text: Fast enough for the human race
  - Black Order of Thüle, The, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Artist: Mal Marc Rude
    Venue: The Music Machine
    Location: [CA?]
    Additional bands or artists: Legal Weapon, The Little Kings, Twisted Roots, SWA, King Kan Mob
    Main text: The Zero One Gallery in association with C. F. Productions presents the Black Order of Thüle
  - Blind Obedience, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Main text: Blind Obedience
    Notes: A 1 x 1.5 in. section clipped out from the left edge.
  - Blondie, 1977; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: Bomp Records
    Location: North Hollywood
    Main text: Bomp Records invites you to meet Blondie "in the flesh"!
  - Blondie, 1975; 8.5 x 14 in. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Venue: Hilly's [CBGBs?]
    Main text: Blondie with the Banzai Babies
    Notes: Stamp and ms. on verso: "Property of: Roberta Bayley…" "Blondie and the Banzai Babies" was a transitional form of Blondie after the breakup of the Stillettos.
  - Boy, 1980s; 42.5 x 30 cm. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Main text: Boy… the strength of the country lies in its youth
    Notes: Poster for the London post-punk fashion boutique Boy.
  - Breakouts, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: 1839 Geary
    Location: [San Francisco, CA?]
    Main text: Breakouts - Free
  - Butthole Surfers, 1982; 8.5 x 7 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: La Grandia
    Location: [Los Angeles, CA]
    Main text: Butthole Surfers + Descendents + Big Boys
  - Buzzcocks, 1977; 15 x 21 cm. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Location: Manchester, UK
    Additional bands or artists: Siouxsie & the Banshees, Penetration
    Main text: Straight music presents: Buzzcocks
  - Carroll, Jim, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Artist: Roger I. Reyes, George Westcott (photo)
    Venue: Mabuhay Gardens
    Additional bands or artists: Mutants, Eye Protection
    Main text: Saturday - [Jim Ca]rrol Group - Jim Carroll and Mutants
  - Cats and Dogs, 6.5 x 10.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Artist: Garrett
    Venue: Antone's
    Main text: May presents - Cats and Dogs - Antone's
  - Channel 3, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: T-Bird Rollerdrome
    Location: Pico Rivera, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Angry Samoans, M.D.C., Sin 34, Deadly Sin
    Main text: That's right Friday night March 11th P.U.N.X. presents the one and only CH3…
  - Channel 3, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: The Godzilla Club
    Additional bands or artists: No Crisis, Crucifix
    Main text: CH3 with Shattered Faith, No Crisis, and Crucifix from S.F.
  - Channel 3, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Artist: [B. Kliban?]
    Additional bands or artists: Shattered Faith, The Vandals, Suicidal Tendencies, Ill Repute
    Main text: See Channel 3 with Battalion of Saints
    Notes: Image on flier is a B. Kliban cartoon, likely appropriated.
  - Channel 3, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Additional bands or artists: J.F.A., Target 13
    Main text: Channel 3 with J.F.A. & Target 13
  - Channel 3, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: The Galaxy
    Location: Fullerton, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Battalion of Saints, Red Brigade
    Main text: Channel 3, Battalion of Saints, Red Brigade … Dor ahad a regular sex life up until last year …
  - Channel 3, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: Club Lingerie
    Main text: KROQ presents Channel 3
  - Charged G.B.H., 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Additional bands or artists: Bad Brains, Scream, Kraut
    Main text: Goldenvoice presents at Perkins Palace - Charged G.B.H. from England
  - Charged G.B.H., 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: La Casa de la Raza
    Location: Santa Barbara, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Code of Honor, Personality Crisis, De-Cry, Kraut
    Main text: Goldenvoice presents at La Casa - Charged G.B.H. from England
  - Charged G.B.H., 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: Fender's
    Location: Long Beach, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Weirdos, MIA, Cro-Mags, Rigormortis, Uniform Choice, Agnostic Front, Verbal Assault
    Main text: Goldenvoice presents at Fenders - Charged G.B.H. with special guests Weirdos
  - Charged G.B.H., 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Additional bands or artists: The Effigies, SSD Control
    Main text: Goldenvoice present Charged G.B.H.
  - Charged G.B.H., 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Additional bands or artists: Vandals, Stalag 13, Love Canal, The Breakouts
    Main text: Goldenvoice productions - GBH
  - China White, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: Monte Carlo II
    Additional bands or artists: Anti, Ill Will
    Main text: China White, Anti, Ill Will
    Notes: The same as the following flier; this copy on yellow paper
  - China White, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Notes: The same as the previous flier; this copy on blue paper
  - China White, 1980s; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Additional bands or artists: Secret Hate, Descendants
    Main text: Your personal invitation to see China White and Secret Hate along with the Descendants all on the same bill at the luxiurious Dancing Waters club in San Pedro
  - Christian Death, 1984; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Additional bands or artists: Flesh for Lulu
    Main text: The Wisdom accompanied by Bleeding: an evening with Christian Death
  - Circle Jerks, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Additional bands or artists: Channel 3, MDC, The Dicks, D.R.I.
    Main text: Goldenvoice presents Circle Jerks - Summer skankoff with Channel 3
  - Circle Jerks, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Additional bands or artists: Agent Orange, Stingers
    Main text: Circle Jerks - On the battlefield - shocking truth - parents are too permissive ...
  - Circle Jerks, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Artist: K. Meek
    Venue: Wolf & Rissmiller's Country Club
    Location: Reseda, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Wasted Youth, Ray Noonan (comedian)
    Main text: Circle Jerks, Wasted Youth + others
  - Circle Jerks, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: Goleta Valley Community Center
    Location: Goleta, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Bad Brains, Wasted Youth
    Main text: Circle Jerks - Group Sex
  - Circle Jerks, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Artist: Brenda S.
    Venue: Reggae Lounge
    Additional bands or artists: False Prophets, Adrenalin O.D.
    Main text: Paul Frederick Productions presents Circle Jerks - Golden showers of hits tour
  - Circle Jerks, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Main text: Circle Jerks - Hey, kids! There's a party for the C.J.'s new LP!
  - Circle Jerks, 1981; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: The Omni
    Location: Oakland, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Necros, Frontline
    Main text: Circle Jerks - Necros - S.J.'s Frontline
  - Circle Jerks, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Additional bands or artists: T.S.O.L.
    Main text: Circle Jerks - The helpless prey of slimy perverts - feel 15 years younger …
  - Clash, The, 1980; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: York Theatre, Fairfax Theatre, El Rey Theatre
    Location: San Francisco, Farifax, and Walnut Creek, CA
    Main text: Grab the future… by its face! … the Clash in Rude Boy
    Notes: Flier advertising screenings of the film Rude Boy, starring the Clash.
  - Controllers, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Additional bands or artists: The Urge, Avengers
    Main text: S.F. - Controllers - The Urge - Avengers
  - Cosmetics, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: Le Disque
    Main text: Cosmetics at: Le Disque
    Notes: With marker sketch on flier image.
  - Costello, Elvis, 1970-1980; A4 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: Apollo
    Location: Ardwick, UK
    Additional bands or artists: Ian Dury, Nick Lowe, Larry Wallis, Wreckless Eric
    Main text: S.U.S.U. ents - Elvis Costello - Stiffs Greatest Stiffs Live at the Apollow in Ardwick
  - Crass, 1980; 17 x 24 in. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Additional bands or artists: Suspect, Nitwits, Inside Nipples, King Bees
    Main text: D...-Day … Suspect, Nitwits & Crass
  - Crime, 1987; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Additional bands or artists: Weirdos, Punts
    Main text: New Wave a u-go-go presents Crime
  - Crime, 1979; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Main text: Crime - Now available - Crime's hot new single - Frustration/Murder by Guitar
    Notes: Promotional flier for Crime's 1977 single "Frustration"/"Murder by Guitar"
  - Crime, 1979; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Additional bands or artists: Dead Kennedys, Zeros
    Main text: Crime - Dead Kennedys - Zeros
    Notes: Same as following flier; on pink paper
  - Crime, 1979; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Notes: Same as previous flier; on white paper
  - Crime, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: Show Case Theater
    Location: Petaluma, CA
    Additional bands or artists: The Impostors, DV8, The Offs
    Main text: New Wave concert … Crime
  - Crime, 1980; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: Savoy Tivoli
    Additional bands or artists: Soul Rebels, C'est la Guerre
    Main text: Savoy Tivoli - Sunday 4th May - Benefit for Target - Crime …
  - Crime, 8.5 x 14 in. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Venue: San Quentin
    Location: [San Francisco?], CA
    Main text: Crime in San Quentin
  - Cro-Mags, 11 x 17 in. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Artist: Sean
    Venue: CBGB's
    Additional bands or artists: No Remorse, Violent Children, the Unwanted
    Main text: Overkill presents the Cro-Mags
  - Crucifix, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Venue: Madison Square Garden
    Location: Phoenix, AZ
    Additional bands or artists: J.F.A., Bunt Toast
    Main text: Crucifix from San Fran. - J.F.A. - Burnt Toast - Reward for the first communist
  - Damned, The, 1986; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: Pall[a]dium
    Main text: Goldenvoice in association with Avalon Attractions proudly welcomes from England - The Damned - Social Distortion
  - Damned, The, 1986; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: Pall[a]dium, UC Irvine Crawford Hall, Fender's, and Santa Monica Civic Auditorium
    Location: Hollywood, Irvine, Long Beach, and Santa Monica, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Social Distortion, The Lords of the New Church, The Jesus and Mary Chain, L.A. Guns, The Joneses, All American Girls, Venom, Exodus, Hirax, Specimen, The Butthole Surfers
    Main text: Goldenvoice presents with pride - in association with Avalon Attractions …
  - Damned, The, 1985; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: 45 Grave
  - Damned, The, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: Vinyl Fetish
    Main text: The Damned - Teatime with the Damned at Vinyl Fetish
  - Dead Kennedys, 1985; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: The Blue Note
    Location: [Denver, CO?]
    Main text: Lanny Coil presents Dead Kennedys
  - Dead Kennedys, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Artist: Gzafix Motozine
    Venue: Russian Centre
    Main text: RRZ Promotions - Dead Kennedys
  - Dead Kennedys, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: B.G.K., Raw Power, Riistetyt, Reagan Youth, Solucion Mortal
    Main text: Goldenvoice presents an international event featuring Dead Kennedys
  - Dead Kennedys, 1980; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: Fort Mason Bldg. C
    Additional bands or artists: Das Blok, Confessions, Little Death
    Main text: The Wave presents Dead Kennedys …
  - Dead Kennedys, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: DOA, Offs, Middle Class
    Main text: Saturday May 26 - Kennedys Dead, DOA, Ofs, Middle Class
  - Dead Kennedys, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: 10th Street Hall
    Additional bands or artists: No Alternative, Circle Jerks, Naked Lady Wrestlers, Warzone
    Main text: Dead Kennedys, No Alternative, Circle Jerks, Naked Lady Wrestlers, Warzone
  - Dead Kennedys, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: Bond International Casino
    Additional bands or artists: Sirens, Bad Brains
    Main text: Dead Kennedys at Bond
  - Dead Kennedys, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: Elite Club
    Additional bands or artists: Exploited, Code of Honor, Black Athletes, Tales of Terror
    Main text: Sat. Jan. 29th - Put Youth to Work Benefit - Dead Kennedys … Peace is Our Profession
  - Dead Kennedys, 1979; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: The Bags, Alley Cats
    Main text: Dead Kennedys - Biafra for Mayor
  - Dead Kennedys, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Artist: A.G.
    Additional bands or artists: Minor Threat, T.S.O.L., Wasted Youth, Crucifix, Circle One, Hüsker Dü
    Main text: Dead Kennedys - July 2nd with special guests
  - Dead Kennedys, 1983; 4.25 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: Devonshire Downs, Cal State Northridge
    Location: Northridge, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Flipper, Youth Brigade
    Main text: Dead Kennedys, Flipper, Youth Brigade + Special guests … Put Youth to Work benefit
  - Dead Kennedys, 1983; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: Flipper, Youth Brigade, Exploited, Channel 3, Vandals, Aggression, Suicidal Tendencies
    Main text: Youth Movement '83 - LA's RRZ & BYO present Put Youth to Work benefit with the only L.A. appearance of Dead Kennedys
  - Dead Kennedys, 1978; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: Germs, Imposters
    Main text: The Dead Kennedys and the Germs with the Imposters
  - Dead Kennedys, 8.5 x 14 in. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Additional bands or artists: Symptoms, Anti-Bodies, Eye Protection, Vs. Jars, Contractions, Pink Section
    Main text: So you're skeptical? Biafra for Mayor Campaign Fund Raiser
  - Deadbeats, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: The Masque
    Additional bands or artists: Dickies, Model Citizens, Spastics
    Main text: Live at the Masque … Deadbeats (demogorgons of dada punk) …
  - Degenerates, The, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Location: [Houston, TX?]
    Additional bands or artists: The Ralphs
    Main text: The Degenerates & the Ralphs (from Dallas)
  - Der Stab, 8.5 x 5.5 in., folded to 4.25 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: La Vida Hot Springs
    Location: Carbon Canyon, CA
    Main text: You are cordially invited to the return performance of Der Stab
    Notes: Folded card
  - Descendents, 1980; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: Anti, Hari-Kari, The Resistance
    Main text: Come see Descendents - Eh! And tell 'em Charlie sent ya.
  - Descendents, 1980s; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: Alpine Village
    Location: Torrance, CA
    Main text: Descendents - Alpine Village
  - Descendents, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: Red Cross [Redd Kross], Anti, The Plebz, Zurich 1916, China White, Secret Hate
    Main text: The Descendents … at the new Dancing Waters
  - Detroit, Dee, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Artist: L. Metz
    Venue: Marina Del Rey Skate Park
    Additional bands or artists: Mad Society
    Main text: At the Marina Del Rey Skate Park - De [sic] De Troit and Mad Society
  - Devo, 18 x 12 in. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Main text: D.E.V.O. - Saturday, May 27, 1978 1:00 PM …
  - Dickheads, The, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: Rock City
    Main text: Wrestling fans: visit the Dickheads
  - Dickheads, The, 1986; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Artist: Cassette (photos)
    Venue: Sound of Music
    Additional bands or artists: Society Dog, Good Samaritans
    Main text: One man-- one audience - Live Performer Johnny Chez & dance to the music from the incomparable Dickheads
    Notes: Ms. marker coloring in blue and red
  - Dickies, The, 1980s; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: The Weirdos, Asexuals
    Main text: Babble-on presents-- The Dickies
  - Dicks, The, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: Rick's Hate Police, Whoom Elements
    Main text: Vasectomy Services of Texas presents (from Austin) (for your listening & dancing pleasure) The Dicks
  - Dicks, The, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Location: [Austin, TX?]
    Main text: Dicks still hate Police - 1982 - Shitty of Austin, Texas
  - Dils, The, 1970-1980; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: Marbles, Blast
    Main text: Dils & Marbles; Blast
  - Dils, The, 1979; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: Contraction, Alley Cats, Crime, the Weirdos, The Go-Gos, Mutants, X
    Main text: Friday Sept. 7 - Dils, Contractions, Alley Cats
  - Dils, The, 1979; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Artist: P.H.
    Venue: The Pit
    Additional bands or artists: Avengers, Negative Trend, Mutants, Dead Kennedys, K.G.B.
    Main text: Jan. 27. Sat - Dils Avengers Negative Trend
  - Dils, The, 1978; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Artist: Evenson; James Stark (front photo), Ruby Ray (back photo)
    Additional bands or artists: UXA, Sleepers
    Main text: The Dils plus UXA & Sleepers
    Notes: Double-sided flier; back advertises a memorial screening of films by "Michael" (11-12-52 to 4-21-78).
  - Dils, The, 1978; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Artist: Roger I. Reyes
    Additional bands or artists: Negative Trend, JJ 180
    Main text: The Dils with Negative Trend and JJ 180
  - Discharge, 1982; 8.5 x 7 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: Aquatic Park
    Location: Berkeley, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Wasted Youth, the Lewd, Circle-One, Hüsker Dü, Batalion of Saints, Jody Foster's Army, Channel 3, Shattered Faith, Deadly Reign
    Main text: Eastern Front: July Aug Sept … Discharge
  - Dischords, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: The Ritz
    Location: Riverside, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Shattered Faith
    Main text: Dischords, Shattered Faith at the Ritz
  - Dischords, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: Roxannes
    Location: Arcadia, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Scoundrelz, Plain Wrap
    Main text: Flyer - Sale price $3.00 - Ingrediants [sic]: Dischords, Scoundrelz, Plain Wrap … Expiration date: Sunday, July 31, 1983
  - Dischords, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Artist: RXCX XIII
    Additional bands or artists: Scoundrelz, Turmoil
    Main text: Neighborhood watch - Dischords, Scoundrels, Turmoil … This is a real punk rock murder Quincy!
  - DOA, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: Vs., Brainiacs
    Main text: From Canada - D.O.A. Vs. Brainiacs
  - DOA, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: 220 10th at Howard
    Additional bands or artists: Adolescents, Middle Class, UK Decay
    Main text: RRZ presents - Sat. 4/11 8pm - D.O.A., Adolescents, Middle Class, UK Decay
  - DOA, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Venue: P.A.L. Boxing Gym
    Location: Pomona, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Agent Orange, Modern 3, Industry, Flash Back, The Mercenaries
    Main text: D.O.A. - Destroy tradition - Agent Orange - Modern 3 - Industry
  - Dogs, The, 1983; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Additional bands or artists: Pegasus, Hoi Polloi
    Main text: Psyclone presents: The Dogs